format of result.quiz_results

{'score': 6,
'total': 10,
'topics': ['CN', 'DBMS', 'DSA', 'OS', 'TOC'], '
results':
    [
    {'topic': 'questions/CN.json',
    'question': 'What is the maximum length of a MAC address?',
    'is_correct': False,
    'user_answer': ' 128 bits',
    'correct_answer': ' 48 bits'
    },
    {'topic': 'questions/CN.json', 'question': 'What is the default port number for HTTP?', 'is_correct': True, 'user_answer': ' 80', 'correct_answer': ' 80'},
    {'topic': 'questions/DBMS.json', 'question': 'What is the purpose of the WITH TIES option in SQL?', 'is_correct': True, 'user_answer': ' To include rows that match the last row in the result set', 'correct_answer': ' To include rows that match the last row in the result set'},
    {'topic': 'questions/DSA.json', 'question': 'Which of the following is NOT a string matching algorithm?', 'is_correct': True, 'user_answer': ' Floyd-Warshall', 'correct_answer': ' Floyd-Warshall'},
    {'topic': 'questions/OS.json', 'question': 'Which of these is not a common UNIX filter?', 'is_correct': True, 'user_answer': ' mv', 'correct_answer': ' mv'},
    {'topic': 'questions/OS.json', 'question': "What is the purpose of the 'useradd' command?", 'is_correct': True, 'user_answer': ' Add user', 'correct_answer': ' Add user'},
    {'topic': 'questions/TOC.json', 'question': 'The language {aⁿbⁿcⁿ | n ≥ 1} is:', 'is_correct': False, 'user_answer': ' Recursively enumerable but not context-sensitive', 'correct_answer': ' Context-sensitive'},
    {'topic': 'questions/TOC.json', 'question': 'The language {aⁿbⁿaᵐbᵐ | n,m ≥ 1} is:', 'is_correct': False, 'user_answer': ' Context-free', 'correct_answer': ' Not context-free'},
    {'topic': 'questions/TOC.json', 'question': 'Which of the following is not a normal form in context-free grammars?', 'is_correct': True, 'user_answer': ' Backus-Naur form', 'correct_answer': ' Backus-Naur form'},
    {'topic': 'questions/TOC.json', 'question': 'Which of the following is true about deterministic context-free languages?', 'is_correct': False, 'user_answer': ' They are not closed under any operation', 'correct_answer': ' They are closed under complementation'}],
'accuracy': [50.0, 100.0, 100.0, 100.0, 25.0, 50.0],
'percentage': 60.0, 'radar_chart': 'image_object'
}


format of exam.quiz_questions
it is a list of dictionaries

[{'topic': 'questions/CN.json',
  'optiona': 'To resolve IP addresses to MAC addresses',
  'optionb': 'To resolve domain names to IP addresses',
  'optionc': 'To route packets',
  'optiond': 'To encrypt data',
  'question': 'What is the purpose of ARP?',
  'questionNo': 9,
  'correctoption': 'A'},
 {'topic': 'questions/DBMS.json',
  'optiona': 'To return the name of the server',
  'optionb': 'To sort the result set',
  'optionc': 'To filter rows based on a condition',
  'optiond': 'To combine rows from multiple tables',
  'question': 'What is the purpose of the @@SERVERNAME function in SQL?',
  'questionNo': 99,
  'correctoption': 'A'},
 {'topic': 'questions/DSA.json',
  'optiona': 'O(n)',
  'optionb': 'O(n + m)',
  'optionc': 'O(nm)',
  'optiond': 'O(n log m)',
  'question': 'The time complexity of Rabin-Karp algorithm in average case is:',
  'questionNo': 52,
  'correctoption': 'B'},
 {'topic': 'questions/OS.json',
  'optiona': 'Display beginning of file',
  'optionb': 'Delete files',
  'optionc': 'Move files',
  'optiond': 'List files',
  'question': "What is the purpose of the 'head' command?",
  'questionNo': 68,
  'correctoption': 'A'},
 {'topic': 'questions/TOC.json',
  'optiona': 'Addition',
  'optionb': 'Multiplication',
  'optionc': 'Ackermann function',
  'optiond': 'Factorial',
  'question': 'Which of the following is not a primitive recursive function?',
  'questionNo': 23,
  'correctoption': 'C'}]

[
{'topic': 'Automata',
  'optiona': 'Addition',
  'optionb': 'Multiplication',
  'optionc': 'Ackermann function',
  'optiond': 'Factorial',
  'question': 'Which of the following is not a primitive recursive function?',
  'correctoption': 'C'},
  {'topic': 'operating System',
  'optiona': 'Display beginning of file',
  'optionb': 'Delete files',
  'optionc': 'Move files',
  'optiond': 'List files',
  'question': "What is the purpose of the 'head' command?",
  'correctoption': 'A'},
  ...
]
